Finding Aid for the Barbara Ann Conlogue Collection of Eleanor Steber Photographs and Clippings, circa 1935-1990
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Prints, circa 1935-1979, I.; Item 001-176
  - Eleanor Steber's home in Port Jefferson, New York, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-119)
  - Eleanor Steber by piano, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-120)
  - Eleanor Steber and her personal representative, Martha Moore Smith, in bathing suits, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-121)
  - Eleanor Steber sitting in bathing suit, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-122)
  - Eleanor Steber and dog, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-123)
  - Eleanor Steber and dog kissing, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-124)
  - Eleanor Steber holding a block of wood, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-125)
  - Eleanor Steber sitting on railing and pointing, undated, 1 3 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-126)
  - Eleanor Steber petting dog, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-127)
  - Eleanor Steber outside a hospital in New York after an appendectomy, reading a get well card from the Steber Music Club, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-128)
  - Eleanor Steber outside large building, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-129)
  - Eleanor Steber, Gordon Eby, Neville Long, and Jack Lewis in front of poster for Tosca, 1956, 1 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-130)
  - Eleanor Steber, Gordon Eby, Neville Long, and Jack Lewis in front of poster for Tosca, used as a Christmas card, 1956, 1 4 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-131)
  - Eleanor Steber by paintings, undated, 1 4 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-132)
  - Eleanor Steber outside with drink, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-133)
  - Eleanor Steber outside reading, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-134)
  - Eleanor Steber outside with drink, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-135)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Vanessa in Samuel Barber's Vanessa, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-136)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Marschallin in Richard Strauss's Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-137)
  - Portrait of Eleanor Steber, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Halsman, Philippe (Box 1, Item ES-138)
  - Portrait of Eleanor Steber, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-139)
  - Eleanor Steber and Dmitri Mitropoulos, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-140)
  - Eleanor Steber and Barbara Ann Conlogue, undated, 1 8 x 10 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-141)
  - Christmas card featuring Eleanor Steber as Sophie in Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 4 1/2 x 5 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-142)
  - Christmas card featuring Eleanor Steber as Fiordiligi in Mozart's Cosi Fan tutte, undated, 1 4 1/2 x 6 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-143)
  - Christmas card featuring Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, undated, 1 2 1/2 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-144)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume, undated, 1 6 1/2 x 4 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-145)
  - Christmas card featuring Eleanor Steber in costume as Countess Almaviva in Mozart's Nozze de Figaro, undated, 1 4 1/2 x 6 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-146)
  - Eleanor Steber singing with piano accompaniment, undated, 1 6 x 7 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-147)
  - Eleanor Steber shaking hands with Barbara Ann Conlogue, undated, 1 6 x 7 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-148)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-149)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella with dog, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-150)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Arabella in Richard Strauss's Arabella, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-151)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Tosca in Puccini's Tosca, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-152)
  - Eleanor Steber in unidentified costume, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-153)
  - Eleanor Steber in unidentified costume, 1955, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-154)
  - Eleanor Steber with husband Gordon Andrews at their wedding, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-155)
  - Eleanor Steber gardening, undated, 1 3 x 4 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-156)
  - Eleanor Steber, husband Gordon Andrews, and friends at an outdoor party, 1963, 1 2 x 3 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-157)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified male at an outdoor party, 1963, 1 2 x 3 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-158)
  - Eleanor Steber (center) with Margaret Ulmer (left) and Ellen Martin at an outdoor party, 1963, 1 2 x 3 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-159)
  - Eleanor Steber, dog and Barbara Ann Conlogue at an outdoor party, 1963, 1 2 x 3 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-160)
  - Eleanor Steber sitting on a brick wall at an outdoor party, 1963, 1 2 x 3 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-161)
  - Eleanor Steber in unidentified costume with man on stage, undated, 1 2 x 3 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-162)
  - Eleanor Steber and Ellen Martin, 1972, 1 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-163)
  - Eleanor Steber and two dogs, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-164)
  - Eleanor Steber singing with piano accompaniment, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 3 1/2 inch black and white photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-165)
  - Eleanor Steber portrait, 1977, 1 3 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 1, Item ES-166)
  - Eleanor Steber at the piano, 1978, 1 3 1/2 x 4 1/2 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Sobel, Marcia C. (Box 2, Item ES-167)
  - Eleanor Steber seated, undated, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-168)
  - Eleanor Steber with flowers at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-169)
  - Eleanor Steber making a face at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-170)
  - Eleanor Steber with Easter flowers, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-171)
  - Eleanor Steber at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-172)
  - Eleanor Steber performing on stage with piano at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-173)
  - Eleanor Steber at Easter talking with unidentified man, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-174)
  - Eleanor Steber with Barbara Ann Conlogue at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-175)
  - Inside of church at Easter, 1979, 1 3 1/2 x 5 inch Color photographic print; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-176)
- Slides, 1958-circa 1970, II.; Item 177-374
  There is no Item 203.
  - Eleanor Steber and Mrs. Whitney, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-177)
  - Eleanor with her parents, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-178)
  - Eleanor Steber and Gordon Andrews, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-179)
  - Eleanor Steber, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-180)
  - Eleanor Steber's father, William Charles Steber, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-181)
  - Eleanor Steber in group shot, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-182)
  - Eleanor Steber, seated, in group shot, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-183)
  - Eleanor Steber, Barbara Ann Conlogue and unidentified man, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-184)
  - Eleanor Steber's mother, Ida Nolte Steber, and Mrs. Whitney, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-185)
  - Gordon Andrews, husband of Eleanor Steber, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-186)
  - Eleanor Steber, Ann (Penny) McInnis (right), and unidentified woman, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-187)
  - Eleanor Steber and Ann (Penny) McInnis, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-188)
  - Eleanor Steber and husband Gordon Andrews in line for food, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-189)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage at Carnegie Hall with Edwin Biltcliffe on piano, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-190)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage at Carnegie Hall with Edwin Biltcliffe on piano, 1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-191)
  - Eleanor and Lucine Amara, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-192)
  - Eleanor and Lucine Amara, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-193)
  - Painted portrait, probably of Steber in Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-194)
  - Painted portrait, probably of Steber in Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-195)
  - Eleanor Steber in her apartment, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-196)
  - Eleanor Steber close-up in her apartment, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-197)
  - Eleanor Steber close-up, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-198)
  - Eleanor Steber close-up, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-199)
  - Eleanor Steber with birthday cake at Cincinnati Manor, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-200)
  - Mrs. Steber, Gordon Andrews, unidentified man outdoors at Eleanor Steber's apartment, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-201)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified woman seated at a table, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-202)
  - Eleanor Steber and two unidentified women seated at a table, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-204)
  - Eleanor Steber seated in her apartment, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-205)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-206)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca and two men, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-207)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-208)
  - Eleanor Steber with a basket of flowers, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-209)
  - Eleanor Steber doing yard work, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-210)
  - Eleanor Steber (center) seated on a patio in Port Jefferson, New York with her husband Edwin Bilby and her personal secretary Helene Carter, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-211)
  - Eleanor Steber seated on a patio in Port Jefferson, New York with husband Edwin Bilby (left) and pianist James Quillian, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-212)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Minnie in Puccini's Faciulla del West, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-213)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume for Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-214)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume for Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-215)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage in a performance of Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-216)
  - Eleanor Steber and two performers from Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-217)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage in a performance of Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-218)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage in a performance of Cosi fan tutte, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-219)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume standing between pianist Edwin Biltcliffe and his wife, Edith Knowles Biltcliffe, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-220)
  - Eleanor Steber standing outside with unidentified woman, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-221)
  - Eleanor Steber on stage in Arabella, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-222)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume for Manon, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-223)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa from Lohengrin, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-224)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume as Elsa from Lohengrin, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-225)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-226)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-227)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-228)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-229)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-230)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-231)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-232)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-233)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-234)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-235)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-236)
  - Eleanor Steber after the opera in her dressing room, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-237)
  - Eleanor Steber after the opera in her dressing room, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-238)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-239)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna in Don Giovanni at the Metropolitan Opera, 4/17/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-240)
  - Poster for performance of Der Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-241)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-242)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-243)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-244)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-245)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-246)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-247)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-248)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-249)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-250)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-251)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-252)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-253)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-254)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-255)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-256)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-257)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-258)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-259)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-260)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-261)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie Therese in Der Rosenkavalier at the Metropolitan Opera, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-262)
  - Eleanor Steber backstage as Marie Therese from Der Rosenkavalier, 3/22/1958, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-263)
  - Lotte Lehmann, Eleanor, and unidentified woman after opera performance, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-264)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-265)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-266)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-267)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital bowing, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-268)
  - Eleanor Steber gesturing to backing orchestra at recital performance, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-269)
  - Eleanor Steber in recital, pink dress, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-270)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified man backstage at recital performance, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-271)
  - Eleanor Steber and unidentified man backstage at recital performance, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-272)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-273)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck backstage with Gordon Andrews, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-274)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck backstage with Gordon Andrews, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-275)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-276)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie from Wozzeck backstage with Gordon Andrews, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-277)
  - Eleanor Steber in costume with unidentified girl on her lap, undated, 1 35 mm color slide; Photographer: Unidentified (Box 2, Item ES-278)